Christopher Wells, Software Developer FR/EN

40A Chemin des **MSc Computing Science** Cornillons **BA Mathematics** 1292 Chambésy

(+41) 22 758 0042 English native 22/04/1992 (+41) 78 648 2009 French C2 Single toph.wells@gmail.com German A2 British, Permis C



Objectives

Having recently obtained my computing degree from Imperial College London, I am passionate about computer programming. I am flexible and have a strong desire to learn, and I would bring these skills to a first significant experience in software development.

Experience

2017-now Mathematics Tutor @ TutorsPlus, individual tutoring $^{1\,month}$ eaching mathematics to secondary school students.

2013-14 Teaching assistant @ University of Lausanne, Operations Management course 6 months Wrote software to randomly generate exam questions. Administered and technical support for computer-mediated exams. Mediation with students over test results.

Maple, JavaScript, CSS, MS Excel

2012-13 Junior Engineer @ St. Noble Company, IT services company

Employee Development of the client's SharePoint site. Creating Web Components, Working with 4 months RESTful APIs. jQuery with the SPServices library. Intern 6 months Modernising old Filemaker database by transferring its data into SharePoint.

SharePoint, HTML, CSS, jQuery, C#, ASP.NET MVC, SQL

2011 Intern @ Metaswitch Networks, telecommunications hardware provider $^{2\,months}\,$ Hardware tests and diagnostics on telecoms servers.

Red Hat Enterprise Linux, Python

Education

2014-17 Master's course in Computing Science @ Imperial College London

Individual project: "Elliptic Curve Cryptography in Secure Multiparty Computing Environments"

Java, SCAPI

²⁰⁰⁹⁻¹² Bachelor's course in Mathematics @ University of Cambridge

2002-09 Baccalauréat @ Lycée-Collège International de Ferney-Voltaire

Hobbies

Video game development: in Unity (C#) and JavaScript. Member of the Swiss Game Developers Association since 2016. Volunteered at the Swiss Game Academy 2017 to coach in Unity.